alfa-gendir.com 2013-05-04

# Privacy - Alfa General Directory

### Alfa General Directory » Privacy

Our service may collect information about you during your visit. This document describes the information we collect and how it is used.

 **Server Access Logs**

Our server logs all requests. The data recorded includes information provided by your browser (user agent and referring page) as well as the requested URI, the time and date and your IP address. The data recorded in these logs may be used for detecting and preventing abuse. We may also collate this data for statistical purposes.

 **Service logs**

The service provided on this web site allows access to external, third-party web sites. We may record your IP address and the web sites you visit. The logs are used primarily for monitoring requests and ensuring no illegal activity is undertaken. Any violations of our terms of use may result in disclosure of the data recorded in our logs to an appropriate third party, which may include your Internet Service Provider (ISP) or local authorities. We may also be required, by law, to provide logs of our service and if requested, such data will be disclosed. We may also use service logs for stastical purposes.

 **Cookies**

Our web site stores a cookie on your computer, if allowed by your browser's privacy settings1. The cookie used by our service uniquely identifies you to the server and allows our web site to remember your preferences.

 **Links**

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookies**

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google's DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [DoubleClick](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx).

We may also use third-party advertising partners on our web site. Advertisers may send you cookies or use web beacons. We have no control over cookies, web beacons or the information collected by our advertisers. Consult the third-party advertiser'Ms privacy policy for more information on their practices.

The service we provide may attempt to forward third-party cookies from the web sites you choose to browse. We have no control over indirect cookies and you are advised to consult the privacy policy of the applicable third-party web site. If you do not wish to receive any such indirect cookies, please disable the _Allow Cookies_ option.

* * *

1| For more information on configuring your browser, see [AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) or the documentation for your browser. We are not responsible for the content of any third-party web sites.  
---|---
